[ Music ]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Hello. I'm Ben Harry from the
&gt;&gt; 大家好 我叫 Ben Harry
Game Center Engineering team.
来自 Game Center 工程团队
In this presentation, I'm going
在这个展示中
to talk about Game Center player
我将谈一谈 Game Center 的
identifiers.
玩家身份标识符
To get started, I'm going to
首先
give you a brief overview of
我将给你们简单介绍一下
what Game Center offers to the
Game Center 为你的游戏玩家
players of your games.
提供了什么
Game Center is a social gaming
Game Center 是一个社交游戏网络
network that allows players to
它可以让玩家
track their best scores on
在排行榜上看到自己的最高分
leaderboards, view their
看到他们在你的游戏中
achievements earned playing your
获得的成就
games, challenge their friends
挑战他们的朋友
to complete an achievement or to
来完成一个成就
beat a leaderboard score, and
或者打败一个排行榜分数
play either real-time or
和他们的朋友们
turn-based multiplayer games
玩实时或回合制游戏
At the heart of Game Center
Game Center 游戏的核心
games are the players.
就是玩家
Players are represented by
玩家是由
objects that contain unique
饱含区分不同玩家
information that differentiate
独特信息的
one player from another.
对象所表示
The object used to represent
代表 Game Center 玩家的
Game Center players is the
对象就是 GKPlayer
Every GKPlayer has a unique
每个 GKPlayer
nickname accessed by the alias
通过 alias 属性都有一个
property.
独特的昵称
A player may also choose an
玩家也可以选择一个
avatar image that will be used
在 Game Center UI 中
within Game Center UIs.
可以用到的头像
In addition, each Game Center
另外 每个 Game Center 用户
user has a unique static
都有一个独特的
identifier that remains the same
静态身份标识符
across all games that the player
这个标识符在玩家玩的所有游戏中都会保持一致
You may use this identifier to
你可以使用这个标识符来
store per-player information.
存储每个玩家的信息
Let me now talk about how a
现在我要谈一谈
player static identifier
一个玩家的静态标识符
currently works in Game Center.
现在是如何在 Game Center 中运行的
You may already be familiar with
你可能对此已经有所了解
this, but let us consider this
不过我们还是来看一下
example in case you need to
这个例子
refresh your memory.
来巩固一下你的记忆
Here we have two teams, Team A
这里我们有两个团队
and Team B.
团队 A 和团队 B
In this presentation, I will be
在这个展示中
using the term team to represent
我会使用团队来代表
a development team that releases
使用 App Store Connect
a game to the App Store using
在 App Store 中
App Store Connect.
发布游戏的开发团队
So, I have been playing two
我在玩团队 A 的两个游戏
games from Team A and I also
同时 我也非常喜欢
really enjoy the game from Team
团队 B 的游戏
As we see, my static Game Center
正如我们看到的
identifier is P123.
我的静态 Game Center 标识符是 P123
Each of these games we'll see
每个游戏都会看到
the same value from my
相同的值
identifier P123.
我的标识符 P123
No matter which game I play, I
不论我玩的什么游戏
had the same static identifier.
静态标识符都是相同的
Going forward, we now want to
下一步 我们想要
increase privacy by introducing
增加隐私性
new player identifiers that are
于是我们新增
scoped to the either the team or
仅用于团队或游戏的
the game itself.
新的玩家标识符
So let's begin with the first of
所以让我们先来
these new identifiers, the team
第一个新标识 teamPlayerID
Remember that team refers to the
请记住 团队指的是
development team that releases a
将游戏发布到 App Store 的
game to the App Store.
开发团队
Again, consider Team A and Team
我们再次以团队 A
B along with the same games from
和团队 B 之前提到的游戏为例
Notice that now I have two
请注意我现在有
different identifiers.
两个不同的标识符
When I play either game from
当我玩团队 A 的游戏时
Team A, the value of my team
我的 teamPlayerID
player ID will be T11.
数值是 T11
When I play the game from Team
当我玩团队 B 的游戏时
B, the value of my team player
我的 teamPlayerID
ID will be T22.
数值是 T22
This means that the value of my
这意味着我的 teamPlayerID
team player ID scoped to the
数值只局限于发布我玩的
team that releases the game I
游戏的团队
This is an improvement to player
这是一个对玩家隐私的改进
privacy as Team A will only know
因为团队 A 只会知道
my team player ID as T11, and
我的 teamPlayerID 是 T11
Team B will only know my team
团队 B 只会知道
player ID as T22.
我的 teamPlayerID 是 T22
So this is the team player ID.
这就是 teamPlayerID
I now want to tell you about our
我现在想要给你们介绍
other new player identifier, the
我们其他的新的玩家标识符
game player ID.
gamePlayerID
The game player ID is unique per
gamePlayerID 是每个游戏中
game per player.
每个玩家都独有的标识符
This means that my game player
这意味着我的 gamePlayerID
ID is unique to each game that I
在我玩的每个游戏中
play.
都是独一无二的
Its value is also independent
它的数值也
from the team that releases the
不受发布游戏的团队约束
Let us go back to our familiar
让我们回到熟悉的两个团队
teams, Team A and Team B.
团队 A 和团队 B
As you can see here, my game
正如你所见
player ID is different for each
不管是哪个团队发布的游戏
game that I play, regardless of
我的 gamePlayerID
which team has released the
在每个游戏中都不一样
To further show how a game
为了进一步展示
player ID is independent from
gamePlayerID 是如何不受团队约束的
the team, let's consider the
我们来考虑一个
case when a game is transferred
游戏从一个团队转移到
from one team to another.
另一个团队的例子
I am now going to show you what
我将为你们展示
happens to my scoped identifiers
当游戏 2 从
when Game 2 is transferred from
团队 A 转移到团队 B 时
Team A to Team B.
我的范围标识符会发生什么
Let's say Team A transfers
比如说团队 A 将游戏 2 的所有权
ownership of Game 2 to Team B.
交给了团队 B
Now, when I play Game 2, my game
现在 我想玩游戏 2
unchanged.
我游戏 2 的 gamePlayerID 还是一样的
My game player ID for Game 2
我游戏 2 的 gamePlayerID
persisted with the game and is
与游戏相连
independent of the team.
不受团队的约束
Now, you may have also noticed
现在 你可能会注意到
something about my team player
关于我的游戏 2 的
ID for Game 2.
teamPlayerID 中的一些变化
My team player ID for Game 2
我的游戏 2 的 teamPlayerID
took on the value for Team B
呈现了团队 B 的数值
since it is now released to the
因为它现在由 B 团队
App Store by Team B.
发布至 App Store
So we have come to the scoping
我们已经讲述了
of the new Game Center
新的 Game Center 标识符的范围
identifiers and also what
以及当游戏
happens to these identifiers
所有权转变时
when game ownership is
这些标识符会发生什么
I am now going to talk about how
现在 我将谈一谈
you may use the scope
你如何在
identifiers in the games that
你开发的游戏中
you develop.
使用这些标识符
As you have seen, we have added
正如你所见
two new scope identifiers to the
我们为 GKPlayer 增加了两个
GKPlayer, the team player ID and
新的范围标识符 那就是 teamPlayerID 和
the game player ID.
gamePlayerID
The team player ID and game
teamPlayerID
player ID have been introduced
和 gamePlayerID
with the goal of increasing
引入的目的就是
player privacy, which aligned to
增强玩家的隐私
the Apple's commitment to
这与 Apple 承诺
protecting the privacy of our
保护用户隐私是吻合的
This new identifiers replaced
新的标识符会替换
the existing static identifier
现有的静态标识符
or player ID on a GKPlayer.
也就是 GKPlayer 的 playerID
The playerID property is now
playerID 属性
deprecated.
现在被弃用了
So I encourage you to start
所以我鼓励你们
using these new scope
使用这些新的范围标识符
As I mentioned earlier, the team
正如我之前提到的
player ID and game player ID
teamPlayerID 和 gamePlayerID
have been introduced to replace
是引入来代替
the static player ID.
静态 playerID 的
If you don't query the player ID
如果你不在你的游戏中
in your games, then you will not
查询 playerID
need to make any changes.
那你不需要做出任何改变
If you do query the player ID,
如果你查询 playerID
you'll need to switch to the new
你可能需要转换到
scoped identifiers.
新的范围标识符
You'll be using the team player
在大多数情况下你会使用
ID in most cases.
teamPlayerID
Likewise, if you currently use
同样地
the static player ID to save
如果你现在使用静态 playerID
game data, you should move to
存储游戏数据
the team scoped ID.
你应该使用团队范围的 ID
Doing so will handle the
这样做可以处理
situation in the device you
多名 Game Center 玩家
shared by multiple Game Center
共享设备的情况
For those of you who may be
如果你们有人
persisting the static player ID
坚持在自己的后端系统中
in your own back end system, you
使用静态 playerID
should also update to the new
你也应该更新至新的
scoped identifiers.
范围标识符
You can do this any time after a
在成功认证后
successful authentication.
你可以随时这样做
Next, let me show you how scoped
接下来 让我来为你们展示一下
identifiers look for their local
范围标识符寻找本地玩家
player as compared to non-local
和寻找非本地玩家的不同
As you probably know, the
你可能知道
GKLocalPlayer is the object that
GKLocalPlayer 是代表了
represents the authenticated
在一个设备上验证过的 Game Center
Game Center player on a device.
玩家的对象
At any given time, only one
在任何特定的时间
player may be authenticated.
只有一个玩家能被认证
And the GKLocalPlayer has a
GKLocalPlayer 有一个
persistent team player ID and
持久化的 teamPlayerID 和 GamePlayerID
But what about the GKPlayer?
那 GKPlayer 又是怎样的呢
A GKPlayer object provides
GKPlayer 对象
information about other players.
提供关于其他玩家的信息
These are non-local players and
这些是非本地玩家
may be found in leaderboards
他们可能会在排行榜中
recently played lists
在最近玩过的名单
multiplayer matches and so
多人模式以及其他情况中出现
The scoped identifiers for
GKPlayer 的范围标识符
GKPlayers will be instance based
会根据使用的
on the context in which they are
环境进行实例化
For example, their scope to each
比如说根据
instance of a leaderboard or
每个排行榜实例
each instance of a multiplayer
多人模式
match, which means that you
这意味着
cannot count on them to persist
你不能依靠它们来
in subsequent matches.
在后续的游戏中持久化
Let's say you have your own
如果你们有自己的
player accounting system.
玩家账号系统
In which case, you'll be loading
在这种情况下
the corresponding GKPlayer
你们会加载相应的
objects.
GKPlayer 对象
To do this, use the
为了实现这个
loadPlayersForIdentifiers:
使用在 GKPlayer 上的
withCompletionHandler method
loadPlayersForIdentifiers:
found on GKPlayer.
withCompletionHandler 方法
You may use either the team
你可以使用
player ID or the game player ID
teamPlayerID 或者
for the identifiers.
gamePlayerID 作为标识符
When you use the new
当你使用新的标识时
identifiers, there is a very
在很罕见的情况下
rare case where the scoped
范围标识符
identifiers will not be
可能会不可用
So what should you do if the
如果范围标识符不可用的话
scoped identifiers are not
应该怎么做呢
Usually, when a player launches
一般来说
one of your games, the scoped
当一个玩家启动你的游戏
identifiers for the local player
本地玩家的
will be available after
范围标识符
successful authentication.
会在成功认证后启用
However, there is a slim chance
然而 也有很小的概率
that the scoped identifiers may
范围标识符可能会不可用
For this case, we've added a new
针对这种情况
API to GKPlayer.
我们为 GKPlayer 增加了新的 API
Scoped IDs are persistent.
scopedIDsArePersistent
This property will be false if
如果它们不可用的话
they are not available.
这个属性就为假
This means that you'll need to
这意味着你需要
check this property before using
在为本地玩家使用 teamPlayerID 或者
the team player ID or game
gamePlayerID 之前
player ID for the local player.
就检查这个属性
So let's tie all this
我们来通过一个
information together by
在成功认证后
considering an example of using
使用范围标识符的
the scoped identifiers after
例子来整合所有信息
As you know, when the
正如你们所知
authenticate handler returns,
当认证处理器返回时
you need to check if Game Center
你需要检查 Game Center
has returned you a view
是否返回了一个
controller.
视图控制器
If so, then you present the view
如果是的话 你需要在
controller when convenient.
合适的时候展示视图控制器
If there is no view controller
如果没有视图控制器
and the local player has
而且本地玩家也成功认证了
successfully authenticated, then
那你就可以
you will be able to use the
在第一次检测到
scoped identifiers after first
范围 ID 是一个持久化数值时
checking the scoped IDs are a
就使用范围标识符
If you are persisting the player
如果你在自己的后端系统中
ID in your own back end system,
持久化 PlayerID
now is when you should convert
现在你应该把
from the old static identifier
旧的静态标识符
to the new scope identifiers.
转换为新的范围标识符
I will now wrap up by
接下来我要总结一下
summarizing what I have
我今天介绍的内容
Game Center is introducing new
Game Center 为了
scoped identifiers with the goal
增加玩家的隐私性
of increasing player privacy.
引入了新的范围标识符
A player's team player ID is
一个玩家的 teamPlayerID
scoped to your development team.
仅限于你的开发团队
A player's game player ID is
一个玩家的 gamePlayerID 限于游戏
persist with that game if it is
如果这个游戏的开发者变了
transferred from one developer
gamePlayerID 依然属于游戏
Use these new scoped identifiers
使用这些 Game Center API 中
in Game Center APIs as you will
新的范围标识符
use the player ID.
正如你使用 playerID 一样
Both of these identifiers are
这些标识符现在都是可用的
available now so start using
所以今天就开始使用吧
For more information on this
了解关于这个演示的
presentation, please visit the
更多信息 请关注
link shown here.
屏幕上的链接
Thank you for watching.
谢谢收看